inlinkz.com 2019-12-25

# InLinkz - Privacy and refund policy

_Effective starting: April 25, 2018_

## Introduction

This statement discloses the privacy practices for fresh.inlinkz.com owned and operated by InLinkz - Aris Kormpetis.

InLinkz takes security of data very seriously and demonstrates its commitment to Your privacy and this policy statement informs you about personal information that is collected and tracked from this web-site and how that information is used.

InLinkz commits to meeting requirements of General Data Protection Regulation ( **GDPR** ) that is in effect since May 25, 2018 by implementing appropriate technical and organisational measures to ensure that data processing is performed in secure manner. We aim to protect Your personal information you provide to us from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access or disclosure.

## Scope of Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to the information that we obtain through your use of InLinkz service that contains of InLinkz web-site InLinkz.com but does not include:

Users owned web-sites or any other Third Party Products customers choose to use in conjunction with InLInkz. You should always review the policies of third party products and services to make sure you are comfortable with the ways in which they collect and use your information.

## Definitions

**Personal Information** : information that may be used to readily identify or contact you as an individual person, such as: name, address, email address, or phone number. Personal Information does not include information that has been anonymized such that it does not allow for the ready identification of specific individuals.

**Web-sites** : InLinkz website, that is accessible via inlinkz.com, its sub-domains (eg. fresh.inlinkz.com) and pages.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any changes, we will notify you by updating the "Effective Starting" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes, we will provide you with additional notice (such as by sending an e-mail notification describing changes summary and providing a link to the full text of Privacy Policy). We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy whenever you use InLinkz Services to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

If you disagree with any changes to this Privacy Policy, you will need to stop using InLinkz Services and deactivate your account(s), as outlined below.

## Information Collected

InLinkz collects Personal Information provided through voluntary registration on our web-site [fresh.inlinkz.com/register](https://fresh.inlinkz.com/register)

What information we collect:

**Account and Profile Information** : We collect information about you as you register for an account, create or modify your profile, make purchases through, use, access, or interact with the InLinkz Services. Information we collect includes:

  * Contact information such as name, email address, mailing address.
  * Billing information such as billing address
  * Profile information such as a username.
  * Information related to your blog/website that may indirectly indicate the spheres of your interests, hobbies, or profession

If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit our website as a guest, but you may be unable to access certain options, features of website’s service, perform payment, etc.

**Content** : We collect and store Content that you upload to InLInkz web-site while using its service. Such Content includes any Personal Information or other sensitive information that you choose to include ("incidentally-collected Personal Information").

**Other submissions** : We collect other data that you submit to our website(s) or as you participate in any interactive features of the InLInkz Services, its customer-support portal, or otherwise communicate with us. For example, information regarding a problem you are experiencing with an InLinkz could be submitted to our Support Services or posted in our public forums.

## Information we collect from your use of InLinkz Services

**Web Logs** : As is true with most websites and services delivered over the Internet, we gather certain information and store it in log files when you interact with our website(s). This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses as well as browser type, URLs of referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, locale and language preferences. Occasionally, we connect Personal Information to information gathered in our log files as necessary to improve InLinkz services for individual customers. In such a case, we would treat the combined Information in accordance with this privacy policy.

## Usage of Third-Party Service Providers

### Google Analytics

We collect analytics information when you use our web-site(s) to help us improve our products and services. On InLinkz web site, this analytics information consists of the features of the InLInkz Service being used, an IP address of the individual who is using the feature (which will include Personal Information if the Personal Information was associated with IP address).

As of the date this policy went into effect, we use Google Analytics as an analytics provider. To learn more about the privacy policy of Google Analytics, refer to [Google's Policies and Principles](https://policies.google.com/). Use the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en) to prevent analytics information from being sent to Google Analytics.

### Service Desk Platform

For more effective management of support tickets we use external Service Desk service FreshDesk from FreshWorks. For more information on FreshWork’s Privacy Policy and compliance with the GDPR requirements, please visit [Privacy Policy page](https://www.freshworks.com/security/) and [Data Protection and Commitment to GDPR](https://www.freshworks.com/gdpr/).

### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

InLinkz uses various technologies to collect information, such as cookies and web beacons. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory. We use cookies to improve and customize experience with InLinkz service; to allow you to access and use the web-site without re-entering your username or password each time; and to count visits and save preferences you set. Your browser can be set to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. The information we collect and analyze is used to improve our service to you.

We want to be sure you understand that accepting a cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any personal information about you.

## How we use Information we collect

**General Uses** : We use the Information we collect about you (including Personal Information to the extent applicable) for a variety of purposes, including to:

  * Register you personal profile and give ability to operate with InLinkz service;
  * Enable you to access and use InLinkz service, including uploading, downloading, collaborating on and sharing Content;
  * Process and complete payment transactions, and send you related information, including invoices and purchase confirmations;
  * Send transactional messages, including responding to your comments, questions, and requests; providing customer service and support; and sending you technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
  * Send promotional communications, such as providing you with information about services, features, offers, promotions; and providing other news or information about us. You have the ability to opt out of receiving any of these communications;
  * Monitor and analyze trends, usage, and activities in connection with InLinkz service;
  * For other purposes about which we obtain your consent.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, we will not use Personal Information appearing in our Analytics Logs or Web Logs for any purpose. The use of Information collected through our InLinkz Services shall be limited to the purposes disclosed in this policy.

## Information sharing and disclosure

We will not share or disclose any of your Personal Information or Content with third parties except as described in this policy. We do not sell your Personal Information or Content.

## Data storage and Privacy Shield Notification

InLinkz hosts data with hosting service providers in the United States. Data hosting provider has been carefully chosen with high security and compliance standards in mind. Hosting provider’s data center is geographically based in the USA and are compliant with [EU-U.S Privacy Shield](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/eu-us-privacy-shield_en) that impose strong data protection obligations on companies receiving personal data from the EU.

## Opt-In

By submitting your Personal Information through InLinkz web-site registration process, you agree to receive communications from InLinkz representatives, including e-mails or other means of communications.

## Opt-Out

You may terminate your account by e-mailing [privacy@inlinkz.com](mailto:privacy@inlinkz.com). We are responsible to removing all information related to you from our systems according to the request. You may choose to opt-out of receiving promotional communications from InLinkz by using the unsubscribe link within each email.

## Our policy towards children

InLinkz Services are not directed to individuals under 16. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information without specific parent’s or the holder of parental responsibility consent, we will take steps to delete such information. If you become aware that a child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us at [privacy@inlinkz.com](mailto:privacy@inlinkz.com).

## Refund Policy

In case of extended (paid) subscriptions, if you are not 100% satisfied with your purchase, within 30 days from the first purchase date, we will fully refund the cost of your order.

## Contact Us

> InLinkz.com
> 
> P.O. Box 157,
> 
> Kardia, 57500,
> 
> Greece
> 
> E-Mail: [privacy@inlinkz.com](mailto:privacy@inlinkz.com)
